Aike Nyan Lynn Oo

Frontend Web Developer

- Thiri Street, Sanchaung,11111 Yangon, Myanmar
- +959979373184
- https://aikenyanlynnoo.github.io/
- in aike.linkedIn
- https://github.com/AikeNyanLynnOo



Profile

Majoring in Software Engineering at University of Information Technology Myanmar, I am really enthusiastic to develop software systems and manage software systems. I have developed various designs for web applications using React, Vue and CSS technologies. I'am also good at building and using REST APIs and currently learning GraphQL. I also have experience of Cloud technologies through Google Cloud Platform (Cloud App Engine, Docker, Cloud Run, BigQuery, Cloud Scheduler, etc.)

Education

Bachelor Of Computer Science

University of Information Technology $\ \ \Box$

Majoiring in Software Engineering

12/2015 – 11/2022

Yangon

Professional Experience

Frontend Web Developer

ONOW Myanmar ♂

Developing content management system using NextJS, Material UI & Redux

Saga, integration with Rest API, User Authentication Management

02/2023 – present Yangon, Myanmar

Frontend Developer present
Freelance Yangon, Myanmar

React, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion, REST API

API Developer

present

Freelance Yangon, Myanmar

NodeJS (ExpressJS, MongoDB, JWT Authentication, Account Registeration,

Account Authentication)

Full Stack Web Developer

HAJ Co.,Ltd ☑

06/2020 – 12/2022 Yangon, Myanmar

Take training and responsible for developing the web applications using React, NodeJS, Docker and Google Cloud Platform (Cloud Technologies - Cloud Run, BigQuery, App Engine, etc)

10/2019

Internship

Ahtar Oo Co.Ltd., □

Yangon, Myanmar

Take training and responsible as a junior web developer using PHP and VueJS

Projects

Mutiple Choice Quiz App

02/2023

Practice

- Choose the specific fields, the difficulty level and time you will take to finish the quiz
- Fully have the control on the test process
- · Able to see how much time is still left to answer the questions
- · Able to end the quiz although the time still left or quiz still remain to answer
- Go freely through the quiz numbers from the quiz panel which is animated, togglable left drawer
- The last but not least, you can see the results and score when you finish the test
- Technologies -> React, Typescript, TailwindCSS, Framer Motion, Travia Quiz
 API ☑
- Repository □

Discord Website Clone

12/2022 - 01/2023

Practice

- Frontend Clone project of Discord business website
- Include all navigation and animations almost the same as original Discord
 Website ☑ at the development time
- Developed **Responsive Design** for all devices
- · Smooth animation as the original website
- Technologies
 - ReactJS (NextJS)
 - Typescript
 - TailwindCSS
 - Framer Motion (for animations)
- Repository □

Web Crawler of Job Hunting Websites

08/2021 - 12/2022

- *Internal system for company*
- Crawl job recruiting websites for competition in market.
- Store crawled information in GCP(BigQuery)

- Query, Research, and Track job opening situations (hiring period, update time, posting end time, employment type etc) using Query(BigQuery)
- Deploy on Cloud Run
- Used Techonologies
 - NodeJS(Express)
 - TypeScript
 - Puppeteer, JsDOM (Third-party libs for crawling)
 - Moment-timezone (To save data in realtime)
 - AmchartJS (data visualization for fail and success rate of crawling for everyday)
 - EJS for template rendering

JKT Myanmar International 🛮

07/2021 - 08/2021

Business Website Design & Backend for job recruiting

- · A business website for my company
- Able to apply jobs over the website
- Used Technologies
 - Vanilla JS
 - Bootstrap
 - JQuery
 - PHP
 - MySQL
 - PHP Mailer (for auto-replying to job applicants)

REST Countries ☑ 08/2021

Practice

- **Search** with country name (full name or part of name)
- Filter with continents
- Light/Dark theme switcher
- Responsive design
- Used Technologies
 - ReactJS
 - TailwindCSS
 - Styled Components
 - REST Countries 🛮
- Repository □

IP Address / Domain Tracker

07/2021

Practice

- Tracking location of server
- Locating in Map when the user input IP address or Domain address.
- Technologies -> React, Netlify functions, **Geo IPify** ☑
- Repository □

URL Shortener ☑ 06/2021

Practice

- Shortening URLs using React, Tailwind CSS & **ShrtCode** □
- Store recent shortened links when user back to app using Browser Storage
- Repository ☑

Certificates

Front End With React (- The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (On Coursera))

Bootstrap Framework (The Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (On Coursera))

Fundamental of Information Technology Engineer (Information Technology Professionals Examination Council (ITPEC))

IT Passport (Information Technology Professionals Examination Council (ITPEC))

Skills			
HTML/CSS	• • • •	Bootstrap/Tailwind	• • • •
ReactJS Redux, Redux thunk, Context	• • • •	NextJS	• • • • •
		Figma	• • • • •
VueJS	• • • • •	NodeJS	• • • • •
Framer Motion	• • • •	Express	
TypeScript	• • • •	РНР	• • • • •
REST API	• • • • •	MongoDB	• • • • •
JQuery, Node-fetch, Axios, GraphQL		BigQuery	• • • • •
MySQL	• • • • •		
Google Cloud Platform (GCP) Cloud Run, App Engine, Cloud Sched	• • • • •	Docker	• • • • •

Interests

Badminton Singing

men-double winner at UIT (2017)

Programming

Table Tennis

Soft Skills

Team Work Fast Learner

Adaptable Open-mindedness

Languages

Burmese English Japanese

Native Conversational N3 Level Conversational